English

Your language: English Español Italiano Deutsch Français Português Nederlands Русский 日本語 Türkçe Ελληνικά Română ▼

Never miss all the cool giveaways:  
get notifications in your browser!

Terms and conditions
====================

The software is required to be downloaded, installed and registered exceptionally during the giveaway period! Please mind that you won't be able to use the contents of the downloaded archive after the end of the giveaway period unless stated otherwise.

Please note that the software you download and install during the Giveaway period comes with the following important limitations:

1. No free technical support;
2. No free upgrades to future versions;
3. Strictly personal usage.

THIS SOFTWARE PRODUCT IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. WITHOUT LIMITATION, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWABLE BY LAW, END USER ASSUMES THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THE DOWNLOADED SOFTWARE PRODUCT.

Privacy Policy
--------------

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which giveawayoftheday.com ("giveawayoftheday.com") collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://www.giveawayoftheday.com/ website ("Site"), and its (giveawayoftheday.com) subdomains.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, the information Users submit by filling out any forms, and other information associated with all sorts of activities or services we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, however, it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. Personally-identifiable information is not collected when a user simply browses the website.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

giveawayoftheday.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

* To improve our Site and services  
    We may use feedback you provide to improve our Site and services.
* To personalize user experience  
    We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services provided on our Site.
* To provide the requested services  
    We collect user’s email to enable downloading of the active Giveaway.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, email and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Data deletion policy

Users can request all or part of their data to be deleted by submitting form at [https://www.giveawayoftheday.com/about/contact/](https://www.giveawayoftheday.com/about/contact/).

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy\_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). By using this Site, you agree to the processing of the information collected from you by Google in the manner and for the purpose described above.

### Changes to this privacy policy

giveawayoftheday.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to check this page for any changes frequently, to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via this form [https://www.giveawayoftheday.com/about/contact/](https://www.giveawayoftheday.com/about/contact/), and we will endeavor to respond to your request.

**Last Updated: September 17, 2015**

© 2006 - 2024 [giveawayoftheday.com](https://www.giveawayoftheday.com/). All rights reserved. Patent Pending.
